Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪Let the daylight
pierce through the night♪
♪Unveiling the dazzling galaxy♪
♪This scorched remnant of myself♪
♪In this world of capricious tides♪
♪That perfect warmth♪
♪You are my only star♪
♪Heartless, obsessed, hopeful, loathing♪
♪How can we escape the regretful pasts♪
♪Watch the sky plunge into the sea♪
♪As dawn's first light
sketches the sky's outline♪
♪Entwined between our fingertips♪
♪When destiny weaves a brilliant net♪
♪Our souls are forged from the shards♪
=Flying Up Without Disturb=
=Episode 6=
Huan Zong?
Come on, help.
- What happened?
- Hurry.
Help me.
What were you doing?
Look at those.
My sect people
gave me those
for self-defense.
I see.
But you rushed out without learning
how to use them.
Exactly.
What should I do now?
It will be a long journey.
You have a point.
I'm worried about it for you.
But thankfully, there's a solution.
That's right.
A master like you
knows how to use them, right?
Want me to teach you?
Yeah, of course.
We're not going the same way.
How can I teach you?
Well...
Will you let me tag along?
Please? Okay?
You want to tag along?
You're in a rush
to find the herbs.
Will I be a burden to you?
Yeah, I need to find the herbs.
Let me think.
You have to think about it?
Huan Zong, just take me with you.
I swear I won't
cause you any trouble.
I thought about it.
I do need your help.
Exactly.
You know
I'm extremely lucky.
I'll definitely help you
find the herbs.
Besides,
I'm injured
and need protection.
That's right.
I may not be as skilled as Lin Hu,
but
it's better
than nothing.
You're right.
But would it
hinder your trials
if you came with us?
Of course not.
Didn't I tell you
my ultimate goal?
You want to be a heroine
who upholds justice
and vanquishes evil
like in the storybooks,
and eradicate injustice
from every corner of the world.
Exactly.
Also,
I told you
that I want to help
every person in need.
Perfect.
Right now, I'm the one
who needs help most.
Exactly.
See?
You won't hinder the trials.
Just bring me along.
We'll help each other.
Alright.
Nice!
Rest assured.
I'll definitely
help you collect
all those herbs.
How did it go?
Senior.
Xiao Dong is looking
into the puppets.
Don't worry too much.
Take a seat.
But I never expected that
Zhong Xi would obtain
the Azure Phoenix Feather so soon.
I must visit
the Zhaohan Sect
to show my gratitude.
But should we hide the fact
that Zhong Xi is injured?
Keep it a secret for now.
That child
carries the hope
of the entire Lingyou Realm.
Everyone
is waiting for his ascension
to breach the celestial barrier
and pave the way
for all cultivators' ascension.
Unfortunately,
he's been fighting the dark cultivators
and missed his ascension window.
If people find out
that his spiritual core is damaged
and he can't ascend,
the cultivators
might lose all motivation.
You are right.
Hurry up.
Inform Zhong Xi immediately.
Now,
where are we going?
We're going to Fengyi
for Cloudseeker Twig.
I really don't know
why we should bring
this annoying girl.
She just offered a phoenix feather.
She clearly wants you
to boost her spiritual energy.
Lin Hu, what are you muttering?
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
Don't listen to him.
I'm not coveting
your spiritual energy.
I swear.
I just think friends should
support each other out here...
I wasn't up to something.
Oh, come on.
It's alright.
Thankfully,
you didn't drag me down.
Huan Zong, you...
Thank you.
Young Master.
It looks like a nice place.
Let's take
a break.
Rest here.
I'll contact Master.
You can do it here.
Why would you walk away?
There's
something we shouldn't know?
Not exactly.
It's just that Master wouldn't
let me go out with Huan Zong.
I have to be discreet.
Remember.
No matter
what you hear,
don't come close.
If Master detects
your presence,
he might rush over
to drag me back,
and I won't be able
to hang out
with you again.
Got it.
Remember. Stay put.
Go ahead.
Master.
It's me, Kong Hou,
checking in on you.
Problem solved
in Qiu City.
Next,
we're heading to Fengyi.
Oh right, Master.
I'm carrying many spiritual tools.
Each can ward off
hordes of monsters.
So please don't worry
about me.
Besides,
I'll be
extra careful.
Young Master, I don't get it.
We're in a rush to find the herbs.
Why are we bringing her along?
The dark cultivators
probably scared her.
Why do you care
if she's scared?
You're just
too compassionate.
You care about her.
But she hides
over there to send
a message.
No matter what,
we're from a respected sect.
Why does she look down on us?
Master Wang Tong
forbids Kong Hou
from regulating my energy
because it might
attract thunder strikes.
Now I get it.
No wonder
he assumed that
I went to find Kong Hou
to help regulate your energy.
Didn't you explain it?
I...
You didn't tell him
that you only wanted to confirm
if Kong Hou returned home safely?
I...
Come on.
You know
back then,
the moment I entered,
that old man tried to kick me out.
What could I
possibly say?
Right, I heard him saying
that
Kong Hou had to regulate energy with you
to play the phoenix-headed konghou.
How could I let her do that?
I was too furious.
So I came back
without explaining it.
Are you done?
Yeah.
Foxes sure talk a lot.
Wait, listen.
Another little rabbit.
Looks delicious.
Brother,
save the tender face for me.
Those fingers must be crispy.
Who are you? State your names.
"State your names".
Take a look.
Why?
Didn't you hear her?
No matter what happens,
we shouldn't go over there.
If you go there,
she might
get angry with you.
If her master sees me,
he'll take her back.
Wait.
Something's wrong.
How dare you
cause trouble in broad daylight?
Don't be afraid.
(Zhou Xiao, Yuanji Sect)
I'm Zhou Xiao, the chief disciple
of the Yuanji Sect.
I'll protect you.
Thank you.
(Jin Ling, Yuanji Sect)
(She's a music cultivator.)
Xiao.
Why don't you stay and fight?
Young lady,
I hope you weren't scared.
Thank you for your help.
I'm Kong Hou from Yunhua Sect's
Qiyue Peak.
Lady Kong Hou
from the Yunhua Sect.
Nice to meet you.
No need for formalities.
Since we came across
those dark cultivators,
we had to act.
Fate brought us together.
Why don't you come and stay
at Yuanji Sect
for a few days?
No, it's okay.
Young lady.
- My friends and I
- Young lady.
have things to do.
We have to go.
Right, Huan Zong?
No rush.
Haven't you always wanted
to play the phoenix-headed konghou?
This lady here
is a music cultivator too.
How about this?
Go seek her guidance.
Go on.
My junior sister Jin Ling
is a renowned
music cultivator.
Why don't you
talk to each other?
Jin Ling?
So you're the 11th
musical cultivator
in the Lingyou Realm.
That's right.
You can't even play
your natal weapon?
It's not like that.
I'm just not proficient yet.
It'll improve with practice.
Since
I'm visiting your sect,
I will seek your guidance.
Come on, let's go.
Young lady.
Our sect is this way.
This way?
After you.
Alright.
Zhou Xiao.
We're Liuguang Sect disciples.
May we also visit
your esteemed sect?
(What if they interfere...)
(But I can't offend)
(the Liuguang Sect.)
Liuguang Sect disciples
are more than welcome.
This way.
Thank you.
Please.
Tiring journey, huh?
Not at all.
We have splendid scenery.
I will definitely
show you around.
Alright.
Jin Ling, what was that?
I missed.
Don't you find
the dark cultivators
a bit strange?
First the dark cultivators.
Then these guys.
Do you think they're related
to the dark cultivators?
It is suspicious.
Look.
This flower carries dark energy.
Why are there such evil things
near the Yuanji Sect?
(Yuanji Sect)
(Master Shuang Qing,
Head of Yuanji Sect)
(Zhang Feng, Son of Master Shuang Qing)
Feng.
With your father's intellect,
our Yuanji Sect
will surely become
one of Lingyou Realm's Ten Great Sects.
You...
Your father...
I know
you're also worried
that this plan
might not work.
But
that useless Yunhua Sect
maintains its position
among the Ten Great Sects.
Besides,
Kong Hou
may be a loser
without a spiritual root,
but she's still
Wang Tong's valued disciple.
If we can snatch her
and make her marry Xiao,
the Yunhua Sect would
have to help promote us
due to our family ties.
Snatch her.
Snatch everything.
Yeah, snatch her.
Come on, Feng.
Let me explain
the plan in detail.
Step one. Hero rescues damsel.
Hero rescues damsel.
First establish
Zhou Xiao, our chief disciple,
as a dashing hero.
Step two.
After Kong Hou returns with him,
have all disciples sing praises
all day long
to make him look admirable.
Don't scribble on it.
Step three is the most crucial.
One decisive blow.
Have Xiao marry Kong Hou.
A devoted wife
follows her husband's lead.
She will become one of us.
I have it all sorted out.
Alright.
Line up to welcome the chief disciple.
I...
I'm too esteemed
to line up and greet him
in person.
Xiao.
Feng.
I've told you so many times.
Look where you're going.
What a rock-solid forehead.
This way.
Senior Zhou Xiao stands tall like a pine
towering above the bushes.
I'm fine.
Senior Zhou Xiao stands tall like a pine
towering above the bushes.
Senior Zhou Xiao...
This here
is Lady Kong Hou from the Yunhua Sect.
We welcome Lady Kong Hou
of the Yunhua Sect.
Your sect people
sure love ceremonies.
The chief disciple
is our guiding figure.
I'd stand at the gate
to greet him every day.
When will you have time
to spar with us?
Jin Ling.
Master told us to do so.
Don't hit him.
Xiao never lets me down.
Who is this?
Huan Zong.
Who is he?
These sect people
are really weird.
Who are those
young fellows?
One's called Huan Zong,
another Lin Hu.
Disciples of Liuguang Sect.
They're traveling with Kong Hou.
(Liuguang Sect)
I couldn't
turn them away
and had to host them here.
This is weird.
Liuguang Sect disciples
can visit anytime they want.
Why did they come
now of all times?
This ruins
my entire plan.
Will you find an excuse
to send them away?
No.
When has the Liuguang Sect
ever respected us?
They're here...
Wait, I'm trying to say...
Well...
These Liuguang Sect disciples
are mere underlings.
For me to visit them
is beneath me.
It'd be a disgrace.
- It'd be...
- Father.
Father.
Have some tea.
Alright.
Good boy.
Xiao.
Let's go play.
Alright, in a little bit.
Jin Ling, let's go.
In a while.
Alright.
Forget it.
Let them stay for now.
Especially that girl
named Kong Hou.
She's a refined and delicate
young lady, right?
We can't let her
feel neglected.
Besides,
I am a respected senior.
She'd surely feel
a bit uptight
if I met her
right now.
Xiao.
You must work harder
and put your heart
into it.
You've worked hard today.
Go back and rest.
I'll take my leave.
Alright.
Jin Ling.
You stay.
Master.
You've lost your senses.
What are you talking about?
There might be a bump on my head,
but my judgment remains sharp.
Especially that Huan Zong.
He's clearly extraordinary.
He's definitely
a senior disciple of the Liuguang Sect.
Jin Ling.
Think about it.
If you marry Huan Zong
and Xiao marries Kong Hou,
then our sect
could gain control
over both the Yunhua
and Liuguang Sects.
I refuse.
This is for your own good.
Understood.
Jin Ling.
I've always treated you
as my own daughter.
Would I ever harm you?
Besides,
didn't you look
closely at Huan Zong?
He's truly handsome.
Xiao is also handsome.
Are you serious?
How can he compare to Huan Zong?
Huan Zong's much prettier.
There's nothing here.
Do you have any food?
Food?
What?
She's from
one of the Ten Great Sects.
A-And she needs to eat?
What did those mediocrities
of the Yunhua Sect teach her?
Master, the problem is that
our sect people
are all fasting.
Yeah.
There's no food.
No one cooks.
Yeah.
She...
Well...
You...
Pass on the order.
Tell all our disciples.
Whoever knows how to stir-fry,
boil, deep-fry, or stew anything
should assemble in the kitchen.
I will reward them handsomely.
- Assemble.
- Rewards await.
Assemble.
Assemble...
Get going.
Not bad.
Pick
the best dishes
for Lady Kong Hou and tell her
that you made those.
Master.
I-I feel guilty
about taking the credit.
It's a strategy.
As the saying goes,
"To win a woman's heart,
you know,
you must first win over her stomach."
My strategy
will work.
To curry favor with Kong Hou,
Master Shuang Qing
is trying far too hard.
Such a sect leader
would mistake a dark cultivator
for a friendly acquaintance.
He's too dumb to achieve
anything.
Young Master.
Let's just
check things out
and devise a plan
after our sect members
arrive.
Those flowers are weird.
Our sect members
might not know what to do.
Lady Kong Hou.
(What's going on here?)
(Are these people as showy)
(as Ling Bo?)
(Never mind. Let's eat first.)
Lady Kong Hou, here.
Did you prepare all this?
I'm not sure
if you like these.
Have some shrimp.
Come on, dig in.
I'm starving. Don't mind me.
Alright.
You're really easy-going.
In our sect,
the dining hall
gets crowded during mealtimes.
You must hurry
to get food.
I've trained for this.
Lady Kong Hou,
I heard your sect has the best scenery
in the Lingyou Realm.
I'd like to visit sometime.
Would you
be willing to
guide me then?
No problem.
I'll have my senior disciples
show you around.
Alright.
Right, Young Master?
That's what I think too.
They're having fun
at this hour at night.
So many candles.
How romantic.
Young Master.
Do you think
Zhou Xiao might fancy
Lady Kong Hou?
In my opinion,
the Yuanji Sect
isn't one of the Ten Great Sects,
but Zhou Xiao's cultivation
matches well
with Kong Hou's.
What do you think?
Got everything?
Get on it.
Alright.
Huan Zong.
You're still up at this hour?
Are you hungry too?
Want some food?
The scallion oil noodles are amazing.
Oh right, you're fasting.
What a pity.
Huan Zong,
why don't you go back to rest?
I'll send you
some spiritual fruits.
If I remember correctly,
you're also fasting.
Our Yuanji Sect
isn't as strict as
the Liuguang Sect.
We have food
every now and then.
It's okay.
Enjoying the moon with you both
is quite pleasant.
In that case,
let's talk together.
Alright.
Zhou.
Strangely enough,
there are dark cultivators
near your Yuanji Sect.
Those dark cultivators are too bold.
I heard
they caused trouble in Qiu City too.
I didn't know
they'd come to Sanshu City.
Unfortunately,
they frightened
Lady Kong Hou.
It's alright.
Didn't you
step forward in time
to protect me?
Besides,
I only met Lady Jin Ling
and had a chance to learn from her
because of the incident.
You're right.
That may be true.
But when did you seek her guidance?
I...
Well...
I was going to see her,
but I was starving
and didn't have a chance.
I'll go now.
It's too late.
Yeah.
It's already nighttime.
You confused me.
I'll go first thing tomorrow.
That's fine.
Want some more?
Go on.
Tiger descending the mountain.
Young Master,
I scouted around the perimeter
and found nothing unusual.
But a courtyard
on the back
has tight security.
Find a way to get in.
Understood.
According to the plan,
Xiao will spend
the day with Kong Hou,
while Ling stays by Huan Zong's side.
Your father
is a genius.
Genius.
I was planning
to show you
and everyone
the scenery of our sect
on flying mounts.
However...
Seniors.
It's fine.
Strolling around like this
is nice too.
Really?
Very well.
Later,
I'll show you
our Eight Trigrams Formation.
And our mines are
longer than Qingfeng Sect's.
Hot springs, Bishui Pavilion.
Our hot springs
are exceptional.
Over there.
Hot springs.
I bet you can cook
lots of eggs at once.
Hot spring boiled eggs
are a signature dish
of our sect.
Next time,
when you visit Yunhua Sect,
let's try
our signature beef noodles.
That's Yong City's
specialty dish.
Alright.
Deal.
Come here.
You're visiting the hot spring?
Yeah.
Do you know
it takes two people to...?
Huan Zong,
if you're not interested,
Jin Ling can show you
the Eight Trigrams Formation.
Jin Ling.
No need.
I like the hot springs.
Let's go.
Huan Zong,
don't force yourself.
I didn't.
Then let's go together.
Together.
What's that flower?
So pretty.
Xiao.
Be careful...
of the thorns.
Huan Zong.
I still feel bad about it.
After all, you got hurt
trying to protect me.
I just asked
the physicians.
They said
you could scratch around
the wounds
as long as
you don't break them.
Got it.
If you can't reach them,
I can help you.
No need.
Go to sleep.
How could I sleep now?
After all, you got hurt
protecting me.
It's fine.
Don't be shy.
Let me help you.
I'm quite good at this.
When my junior disciples
had rashes,
I helped them.
It feels great.
Try it and you'll see.
Go back.
Have fun with Zhou Xiao.
Won't you boil some eggs together?
We can do that anytime.
We agreed to do it
tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah.
Don't drive me away.
Let me scratch your back.
Get out.
Feel better?
Well?
Come on, stay put.
This is medical treatment.
Why are you scared?
This is ice.
It helps reduce swelling.
Don't tell me
you're still shy at this moment?
Besides,
didn't you say that
genders come next to
saving lives?
In such situations,
it's acceptable.
But you shouldn't normally do that.
What's wrong with that?
For example,
we can be close to each other
because we're friends.
But Zhou Xiao is not your friend.
Senior Zhou Xiao
is also my friend.
When did you
become friends?
We should take care
of each other.
We're all friends.
Then what am I?
We're friends too.
I'm also your friend?
But let me tell you a secret.
You are
different from Senior Zhou Xiao.
You're very, very important
to me as a friend.
"Very, very important."
How important exactly?
If I have to rank you
by your significance,
Senior Zhou Xiao
would be around tenth place,
while you're second.
So who's first?
First place?
Senior Ling Hui, of course.
Although she's
Master Pei Huai's disciple,
we grew up
together.
And she showed me
how to make spirit stones.
Second place is acceptable.
Huan Zong,
you care about rankings?
What a child.
So adorable.
Feeling better?
No.
You're clueless.
Liuguang Sect disciples
came visiting.
If we rushed to meet them
right away,
we would
lose our status.
But
he's injured now.
As the sect leader,
I'm going to
check on him.
It shows the manners of a major sect.
Huan Zong needs to rest now.
He can't interfere with
your interactions with Kong Hou.
I think
he got injured at the perfect time.
Feeling better?
Yeah.
Say something.
How am I supposed to know
if the pressure is fine?
Master, they...
Xiao.
What do you think
about what happened?
Master,
I dare not think about
what happened.
You dare not think about it?
Useless.
Ouch.
Why can't you appeal to her?
That Liuguang Sect disciple
managed to charm
this lady.
There is
something between them.
Let's just give up.
Yeah.
Give up?
You blockhead.
We're not giving up.
How can we quit now?
Listen carefully.
Let me analyze this for you.
Who saved Kong Hou?
Huan Zong did.
Yeah, Huan Zong saved Kong Hou
and got injured in the process.
Naturally, she will care for him.
Such an interaction
creates something.
Now I get it.
No, you don't.
What did you get?
I didn't get it.
Listen.
I believe
that Kong Hou
is into someone
who makes her feel secure
yet also reveals
his vulnerable
side.
Master.
Didn't you
marry your ex-wife about
two centuries ago?
Two and a half centuries.
That would have been
a long time ago
for mortals.
Generations ago.
Are you sure your methods still work?
Think about it.
You saved Kong Hou once.
She's going to feel
secure around you.
Now...
You need to get injured.
Master.
It hurts.
Is this a martial contest?
- Master.
Sorry I'm late.
This must be
the renowned
Lady Kong Hou of the Yunhua Sect?
You must be Master Shuang Qing?
That's me.
I pay respects to Master Shuang Qing.
Good girl. So polite.
Our Yuanji Sect
holds annual martial contests.
Perfect timing for you
to observe.
Alright.
Make yourself at home
at Yuanji Sect.
Prepare for the contest.
- Alright.
- Go for it.
You got this.
Go for it.
Go!
Go for it!
Come on!
♪Roaming with the wind♪
♪Wandering about♪
♪A final ember of warmth abides♪
♪Absurd plots unfold♪
♪Mere spectators♪
♪Footprints left on shores♪
♪Fickle kisses burn♪
♪Withering in an instant♪
♪Lanterns glow, depicting her grace♪
♪Like rusted locks♪
♪Chaining our memories♪
♪Only scars remain♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪Love is mystery♪
♪So be it♪
♪She blazes uncontrolled♪
♪A sickness of the soul♪
♪Cold nights take their toll♪
♪So be it♪
♪All efforts go unrewarded♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪So be it♪